<resources>
    <string name="app_name">TopAppBar</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>

    <string name="long_text"> Shewing met parties gravity husband sex pleased. On to no kind do next feel held walk. Last own loud and knew give gay four. Sentiments motionless or principles preference excellence am. Literature surrounded insensible at indulgence or to admiration remarkably. Matter future lovers desire marked boy use. Chamber reached do he nothing be.

Needed feebly dining oh talked wisdom oppose at. Applauded use attempted strangers now are middleton concluded had. It is tried ﻿no added purse shall no on truth. Pleased anxious or as in by viewing forbade minutes prevent. Too leave had those get being led weeks blind. Had men rose from down lady able. Its son him ferrars proceed six parlors. Her say projection age announcing decisively men. Few gay sir those green men timed downs widow chief. Prevailed remainder may propriety can and.

Much did had call new drew that kept. Limits expect wonder law she. Now has you views woman noisy match money rooms. To up remark it eldest length oh passed. Off because yet mistake feeling has men. Consulted disposing to moonlight ye extremity. Engage piqued in on coming.

Man request adapted spirits set pressed. Up to denoting subjects sensible feelings it indulged directly. We dwelling elegance do shutters appetite yourself diverted. Our next drew much you with rank. Tore many held age hold rose than our. She literature sentiments any contrasted. Set aware joy sense young now tears china shy.

It as announcing it me stimulated frequently continuing. Least their she you now above going stand forth. He pretty future afraid should genius spirit on. Set property addition building put likewise get. Of will at sell well at as. Too want but tall nay like old. Removing yourself be in answered he. Consider occasion get improved him she eat. Letter by lively oh denote an.

At every tiled on ye defer do. No attention suspected oh difficult. Fond his say old meet cold find come whom. The sir park sake bred. Wonder matter now can estate esteem assure fat roused. Am performed on existence as discourse is. Pleasure friendly at marriage blessing or.

Prevailed sincerity behaviour to so do principle mr. As departure at no propriety zealously my. On dear rent if girl view. First on smart there he sense. Earnestly enjoyment her you resources. Brother chamber ten old against. Mr be cottage so related minuter is. Delicate say and blessing ladyship exertion few margaret. Delight herself welcome against smiling its for. Suspected discovery by he affection household of principle perfectly he.

On insensible possession oh particular attachment at excellence in. The books arose but miles happy she. It building contempt or interest children mistress of unlocked no. Offending she contained mrs led listening resembled. Delicate marianne absolute men dashwood landlord and offended. Suppose cottage between and way. Minuter him own clothes but observe country. Agreement far boy otherwise rapturous incommode favourite.

Real sold my in call. Invitation on an advantages collecting. But event old above shy bed noisy. Had sister see wooded favour income has. Stuff rapid since do as hence. Too insisted ignorant procured remember are believed yet say finished.

Manor we shall merit by chief wound no or would. Oh towards between subject passage sending mention or it. Sight happy do burst fruit to woody begin at. Assurance perpetual he in oh determine as. The year paid met him does eyes same. Own marianne improved sociable not out. Thing do sight blush mr an. Celebrated am announcing delightful remarkably we in literature it solicitude. Design use say piqued any gay supply. Front sex match vexed her those great.
</string>

</resources>